And so, having completed their promised kiss, the two began a journey beyond Severance, guided by the Star of Love.
Hey, Mommy, what's your new book going to be about?
It's the story of you and your friend, the girl who taught us all about Kumaria. This is the last page.
Huh? I don't know what girl you mean.
Of course you know what girl. She's the one you love. Don't you remember telling me you sang the love song together?
I don't know any girl like that.
What? Oh, Kureha, what's happened? Don't tell me you've forgotten her.
From the beginning, we hated you. But also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you. So we had to cross the wall.
You're in Kuma!
You're in Kuma Harashi!
It was amazing. I wish she could have seen the look on Kureha's face.
I didn't expect it to feel so good.
Thank you for choosing me from the crowd.
You found me, and I love you.
I'm not a weak girl at the mercy of the invisible storm anymore.
I'm far too important, and we'll never get excluded now. It's wonderful.
Chuck!
Simmer, simmer, porridge, simmer, simmer, softly. Growl, growl, growl.
After Ginkgo saved her letter, Curry Pie gave us official permission to freeload at her house.
We're so close now, Lulu can almost taste it.
Ginkgo's gone through a lot, but it seems like it's just a matter of time before she gets her promised kiss.
It won't! I'll never back down on love!
I don't understand. Why would you protect Sumika's letter for me?
Why, when it cost you so much?
Ginkgo, oh good. I'm glad you're awake.
If you want, I can tell you all about my love.
Oh.
As long as you don't forget, love, you'll never, ever be truly alone.
And if you don't give up on love, even if you lose something, you'll never be invisible.
Wait, how do you know those words?
You are and have always been my Lady Kumaria.
Your Lady Kumaria?
Like the one from Mom's book?
Delicious smell. You smell, Kareha.
Growl, growl.
You need to search. You need to find what you want.
But does what I want need to be found?
Yes.
I don't know what to look for, and I don't know where to find it.
I know you remember. It's in your fingers, in your lips.
It's inside you, right here.
Please, will you give me the promise kiss?
Promise kiss? From me to you?
And me to you.
Then everything will awaken, and it will all change.
Whoa. What was that?
Oh, wow. What a thing to dream.
Growl. The honey porridge is ready.
Is everything all right?
You're blushing, curry pie.
Just your imagination.
You don't mind keeping your eye on Ginkgo, do you?
She's sweating a lot.
Thanks.
Growl.
My lady, Kumari.
What would I dream that for?
Kareha, did you have fun with your friend again today?
Yep. Guess what, Mom?
I taught her how to sing the love song.
Oh, my. You did?
Uh-huh. It's because she's my special friend.
So I figured she gets an exception.
I see. You really love her, don't you, sweetie?
Yeah, I do.
Her? Who is her?
Maybe...
How could I forget?
I did have a friend.
Mom, please help me.
Who was that girl?
I think I'm starting to remember.
I heard there was another bear attack.
No way. Wasn't it exterminated, though?
I thought that girl shot it.
You know, what's her name?
Oh, yeah.
The one who attracts bad luck to, like, everyone.
Whether she did or not,
I'm telling you, another girl from her class totally got attacked.
For real?
For real.
So, who was it this time?
What?
Kaoru Harishima?
Yes, she was discovered this morning in front of the flower bed.
They declared it a bear attack based on the poor girl's injuries.
But how?
Oh, I thought I shot that bear.
Which means, unfortunately, there's yet another bear still roaming the halls of this school.
It's horrifying.
The bears didn't just take Rea's life.
They stole the proof of our love.
They took the star pendant I gave her.
Oh, Miss Yuriyika.
The bear with Rea's pendant.
That one is our mortal enemy.
One day we'll find it.
And then...
And then I'll kill it.
I'm so sorry.
You came here to ask me about something, didn't you, dear?
Yes.
It's about an old friend.
I'd like to know what you know.
An old friend of yours?
Right.
I remembered her while I was listening to Mom's music box.
When I was younger, apparently I had a friend who was very special to me.
I know this girl is her.
But for some weird reason, I can't remember her face or her real name.
I was hoping you might know something more about my friend.
Come to think of it, Rea made a rather strange comment once.
It was shortly before she died, I think.
She told me you had suddenly and completely forgotten about a close friend.
Huh?
What else?
Ah, yes, her last book.
The Moon Girl and the Forest Girl.
She said she wrote that story about you and that forgotten girl.
Mom's last book was about me and my friend?
Ginkgo, hang in there.
Sniffle-grow, your fever's not going down.
Lulu knows.
This will turn you into a nice cold growl-sicle and you'll feel way better.
Lulu is so clever.
Kumariya is love.
As the world's mother, she is the one who approves all living things and gives them love.
The cub who appeared the day of that silvery blizzard was named Ginkgo.
You're an unwanted bear, you know.
A lonely lone wolf's bane that'll never be wanted by anybody.
Hey, what's this about?
What, you think you're the lone wolf's bane princess?
Lone wolf's bane.
Kurosuke!
Shut up!
And so Ginkgo was left all alone.
For obvious reasons, she became known as Ginkgo the Lone Wolf's Bane.
I understand now.
This world is ruled by power.
No one will ever be kind to the weak ones.
It's a dog-eat-dog world and bear-eat-salmon.
Kumami, dinner time!
Okay!
Kumako, come back home!
Kumari!
Okay!
Kumagaret!
Kumakaron!
Okay!
Kumakaron, today's your favorite!
Salmon pizza!
Hooray!
I love salmon pizza!
You are just so adorable!
Eventually, the day of severance came.
Bear cubs and Ginkgo's situation were gathered up by the superior, Lady Coomaster.
Rejoice, my children, for you have finally been found.
Yes, surely you are unwanted bears, but now you shall be given a chance at approval.
In this world, only one needs you and gives you approval.
We thank her daily for her love and graciousness.
Thank you, Lady Kumaria!
Lady Kumaria?
From this day forth, you are cubs of Kumaria.
You shall be guard bears and defend the great boundary between bear and human.
Exclude the vermin known as humans from our border and eliminate them in order to protect
our world.
That is the mission you shall carry out for us, for we are the ones loved by Holy Mother
Glomaria!
Growl!
Ah!
Human excluded!
Growl, growl!
Growl!
Ah!
Human excluded!
Growl, growl!
Growl!
Human excluded!
Growl, growl!
HQ, HQ, request backup immediately!
Oh, please!
Mary McClurdy!
Ginkgo believed if she fulfilled her mission,
surely Kumaria would approve of her
and she would one day be granted love.
I'm not an unwanted lone wolfsbane.
I'll keep eating more and more people
and someday I'll get approved.
Soon enough, Lady Kumaria will do it.
I'll finally be granted my love.
There must be an amazing world beyond that sky.
Day after day, the moon girl and the forest girl looked at the sky.
I wonder if the forest girl must be her.
Oh, I just don't know.
Hello?
Curry Pie, you're here!
Uh, yep.
Welcome home!
Thanks, Lulu.
Growl!
What book is that?
It's a picture book my mom wrote.
How cool!
May Lulu read it?
Yes, of course.
But I'll warn you, it doesn't have an ending.
Why doesn't it have one?
Because my mom died before she got the chance to finish it.
She was killed by a bear.
Go ahead, I can check on Ginkgo.
Tell me, Ginkgo.
Ginkgo loves you so much! Look at what she's done for you!
Why?
We only just met each other.
And I haven't done anything for you.
Your injuries and your pain should have been mine.
But you sacrificed yourself anyway.
No way she's not done for.
Either way, she'd slow us down.
Let's exclude her.
Exclude her.
The animal world is merciless.
The weak, the scared, the ones who can't keep constant within the group.
They are summarily excluded.
Oh no.
It looks like I failed.
Unwanted bear.
You are a lone wolfsbane.
Goodbye.
A lone wolfsbane.
So I don't get to be chosen then.
I don't get to be approved by anyone.
I don't get to be loved.
I'm going to die here without ever being found.
This is the love song my mom taught me.
It's okay.
I'm your friend.
You don't have to be alone anymore.
I'm here now and I love you.
Lady, come on.
I don't get to be loved.
I'm going to die here without ever being found.
This is the love song my mom taught me.
It's okay.
I'm your friend.
You don't have to be alone anymore.
I'm here now and I love you.
Lady Kumariya?
Kumariya.
From the book.
You know it, don't you?
But how?
Kureha.
Well, this is great.
I'm glad you're awake.
Don't go.
You were singing something.
Um...
I, uh...
I need to go tell Lulu you woke up.
Growl!
It's almost done!
Growl, growl!
Ginger milk is on its way to completion!
Lulu just needs to mix in lots and lots and lots of honey.
Then the yummy ginger milk will be all done!
There!
All done!
You two enjoy it together, okay?
Yay!
Growl!
Oh my!
You two really love honey ginger milk, don't you?
Yeah!
That's because it's the flavor of our love!
Koreha?
You spaced out!
I just remembered it.
The ginger milk.
Huh?
Yeah, my mom made it.
And we drank it here.
She gave it to me and a friend of mine a long time ago.
Ha!
I'd forgotten how that felt.
A memory can change so much.
Like now, I feel happy again.
Lulu knows why.
It's because of the honey ginger milk.
That's actually Ginko's love flavor.
You're spaced out.
You're spaced out!
I just remembered it.
The ginger milk.
Huh?
Yeah, my mom made it.
And we drank it here.
She gave it to me and a friend of mine a long time ago.
Ha!
I'd forgotten how that felt.
A memory can change so much.
Like now, I feel happy again.
Lulu knows why.
It's because of the honey ginger milk.
That's actually Ginko's love flavor.
It's the flavor that tells her she's not all alone in the world.
That she matters to someone.
The taste of a twinkling star.
Her love flavor?
Is honey ginger milk?
No!
Lulu hasn't added the honey to finish this off yet,
so she needs to go get some.
Lulu will be right back!
I don't understand.
How could I forget a friend I cared about so much?
I remember now that I loved her a lot.
But why?
Honey ginger milk will get Ginko and Curry Pie totally close in no time at all!
Lulu is so clever!
Oh yeah, Curry Pie's mom's book.
The moon girl and the forest girl?
Kureha!
Are you trying to tell me the moon girl is supposed to be Kureha?
Then would that make Ginko the forest girl?
Probably.
Once upon a time, the worlds were divided into two parts by the sky.
There was the moon world?
And the forest world.
I am sorry, but you may not, said Kumariya.
For the two worlds have been severed forever.
Wanting to cross that severance is pride.
Hold on.
This is my mother's love song.
There is one way to make your wish come true.
If your love is true, your friend will be waiting for you.
You'll find her on the other side of that door.
in the other side of that side of that door...
lane
Kumariya asked the two girls a question.
Is your love the real thing?
I found you.
You're her, aren't you?
You're my old friend.
Growl, giggle.
Okay, Lulu's special honey ginger milk is complete.
Growl?
What's this?
Criminal bear?
Ginko Yurishiro, I know all about the grave crime you committed.
I know what you did.
You were the one who...
Ginko!
Oh, this can't be true.